<!--

-->

<TutorialScript>
	

	<TutorialStep object="" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="true" quadrant="2" centerOnCharacter="Edward">
		<![CDATA[It's Tuesday morning, and Edward's got a conundrum.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	
	<TutorialStep object="" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="true" quadrant="2" centerOnCharacter="Edward">
		<![CDATA[(At first he thought he just had a problem, but then found 'conundrum' in an online thesaurus and liked that much better. Although he still can't remember how to spell it.)]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	
	<TutorialStep object="" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="true" quadrant="2" centerOnCharacter="Edward">
		<![CDATA[Edward's canondrum is this: he's not sure who he is any more.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	
	<TutorialStep object="" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="true" quadrant="2" centerOnCharacter="Monica">
		<![CDATA[I mean, back in the day he was one of the popular kids. He even used to date Monica. Maybe this goth thing has just been a phase.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	
	<TutorialStep object="" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="true" quadrant="2" centerOnCharacter="Mave">
		<![CDATA[Although his fellow classmates would be shagrinned to know this. After all, he and his girlfriend Mave DEFINE goth for most of the school. Could he give that up?]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	
	<TutorialStep object="" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="true" quadrant="2" centerOnCharacter="Phoebe">
		<![CDATA[The endless war with the emos like Phoebe is getting old, too. Maybe they aren't so different after all. Is it time to bury the hatchet... ]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	
	<TutorialStep object="" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="true" quadrant="2" centerOnCharacter="Oswald">
		<![CDATA[...or to sharpen it? Because the part of Edward that hated being popular has always wanted to bring his old crowd down. Could there be a goth revolution? Could the old order be overthrown and a new power rise?]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	
	<TutorialStep object="" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="true" quadrant="2" centerOnCharacter="Edward">
		<![CDATA[To do that, Edward's going to need a lot of friends... or a lot of people who think he's cool. Is it possible in just four days?!]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	
	<TutorialStep object="" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="false" quadrant="2" stop="true">
		<![CDATA[Whatever happens, it will indoobitabilly be a most exitudinal week for Edward. Definitely no time to review that feedback from the English teacher.]]>
	</TutorialStep>

	
</TutorialScript>