


<TutorialScript>
	
	<TutorialStep object="" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="true" >
		<![CDATA[Prom Week characters can be in one of three relationship types with each other: friends <span color='0xFFFF00' >FRIENDS</span> , dating <span color='0xFFFF00' >DATING</span> , or enemies <span color='0xFFFF00' >ENEMIES</span> . These are each like light switches... they're either on or off for each pair of characters.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="true" >
		<![CDATA[But characters have more complicated feelings about each other, too. Someone might have high <span color='0x00FF00'>buddy</span> feelings towards a friend, meaning he likes her a lot, but she may only have average or even actively negative buddy feelings for him.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="true" >
		<![CDATA[Feelings affect many of the things the characters do... such as who they like to stand next to.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="avatar" name="oswald" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="false" >
		<![CDATA[See if you can find Oswald (in the tennis outfit) on this level. You may have to click-drag or scroll to zoom out to find him (he likes standing a looong way from the Goths). Click on Oswald when you find him.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="avatar" name="edward" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="false" >
		<![CDATA[Now find Edward (in the top hat) and click him.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="relationshipSummaryButton" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="false" quadrant="2">
		<![CDATA[When two characters are selected, you can see the relationships and feelings they have for each other by clicking the relationship summary box underneath the first exchange in the ring. (In this case it's just under 'Show Off.' Click the summary box now.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="true" quadrant="1" >
		<![CDATA[The bottom window shows how the two selected characters feel about each other. Green lines indicate <span color='0x00FF00'>buddy</span> feelings. Looking at the lengths of the two green arrows, we can see that both Oswald and Edward are pretty indifferent to each other.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="true" quadrant="1" >
		<![CDATA[The pink lines indicate <span color='0xFF9999'>romantic</span> feelings. Again, very little interest from either party.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="true" quadrant="1" >
		<![CDATA[Finally, the blue lines show <span color='0x0000FF'>coolness</span>. Oswald thinks Edward is really cool (must be the hat!) although Edward couldn't care less about Oswald.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="avatar" name="edward" eventType="deselect" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="false"  quadrant="1">
		<![CDATA[Click on the background to deselect Edward as the secondary character.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="avatar" name="mave" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="false"  quadrant="1">
		<![CDATA[Click on Mave (with the green eyes and black hair).]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="true" >
		<![CDATA[Wow, Oswald and Mave don't like each other at all (in fact they are enemies <span color='0xFFFF00' >ENEMIES</span> ) ... although they do seem to appreciate each others' coolness.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="socialGameButton1" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="false" quadrant="2">
		<![CDATA[A character's feelings will be reflected in the social exchanges he or she wants to play. Notice that Oswald wants to play a blue <span color='0x0000FF'>Cool Up</span> exchange with Mave, as well as several green <span color='0x00FF00'>Buddy Down</span> exchanges. Click on 'Annoy.']]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="initiatorIntentGroup" name="" eventType="over" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="false" >
		<![CDATA[Exchanges with up or down arrows will change how the second character feels about the initiator. The bottom window shows us more information. Click 'Intent' if that's not the view you're on, then move your mouse over the icon with the green down arrow.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="goButton" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="false" disableExceptionsButStillProgress="socialGameButton1">
		<![CDATA[The pop-up text confirms that Annoy is a <span color='0x00FF00'>buddy down</span> exchange: if Mave accepts, her buddy feelings for Oswald will drop even further. Click the play button to try this exchange.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="detailsButton" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="false" quadrant="3">
		<![CDATA[Oswald's intent was to Annoy Mave, and Mave accepted (she was annoyed). Let's click the 'Details' button in the bottom center of the results window to learn why.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="continueButton" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="false" quadrant="3">
		<![CDATA[Click the 'Factors' button to see why Mave accepted this exchange. Sure enough, her low buddy feelings for Oswald made her want to accept exchanges that would lower her negative feelings more. Click the continue button.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="avatar" name="mave" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="false" quadrant="1">
		<![CDATA[Let's look at a more interesting example. Click Mave.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="avatar" name="edward" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="false" quadrant="1">
		<![CDATA[Now click Edward.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="true" quadrant="1">
		<![CDATA[The bottom window shows us something interesting: though Mave and Edward are dating <span color='0xFFFF00' >DATING</span> , her <span color='0xFF9999'>romantic</span> feelings for him are much higher than his are for her. This might indicate that Edward is getting bored with the relationship.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="socialGameButton1" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="false" quadrant="1">
		<![CDATA[Click 'Woo,' a <span color='0xFF9999'>romance up</span> exchange. We can guess that Edward's low romantic feelings mean he might reject Mave's advance.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="goButton" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="false" disableExceptionsButStillProgress="socialGameButton0">
		<![CDATA[Click the play button or 'Woo' again to start the scene.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="true" quadrant="3" >
		<![CDATA[Sure enough, Edward rejected Mave's attempts to 'Woo.' Looks like this relationship is hanging by a thread.]]>
	</TutorialStep>
	<TutorialStep object="" name="" eventType="click" preText="" postText="" disableExceptions="" nextVisible="false" isOver="true" >
		<![CDATA[Feelings show why characters behave in certain ways. In the next tutorial we'll look at more ways of figuring out what characters are thinking and how to influence their behavior.]]>
	</TutorialStep>	
	
	
	

</TutorialScript>